Guide to the John R. Mott Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- General Correspondence, Series I
  - Alphabetical listing
    - Koo, V.K. Wellington, 1918 (Box 47, Folder 877)
    - Kraemer, Hendrik, 1931-1951 (Box 47, Folder 878)
    - Kresge, Anna, 1929-1947 (Box 47, Folder 879)
    - Kung, H.H., 1943-1949 (Box 47, Folder 880)
    - Lac - Lap (Box 47, Folder 881)
    - Lar - Lay (Box 47, Folder 882)
    - Lea - Lem (Box 47, Folder 883)
    - Leo - Lew (Box 47, Folder 884)
    - Lib - Lig (Box 47, Folder 885)
    - Lim - Ll (Box 47, Folder 886)
    - Lob - Lon (Box 47, Folder 887)
    - Loo--- Lot (Box 47, Folder 888)
    - Lou - Ly (Box 47, Folder 889)
    - Laidlaw, Robert, 1913 (Box 48, Folder 890)
    - Lake Mohonk Mountain House, 1940-1948 (Box 48, Folder 891)
    - Lake Placid Club, 1940-1954 (Box 48, Folder 892)
    - Lambuth, W.R., 1913-1915 (Box 48, Folder 893)
    - Lampe, M. Willard, 1940-1942 (Box 48, Folder 894)
    - Lamplough, W., 1910-1920 (Box 48, Folder 895)
    - Lane, Franklin K., 1916-1919, nd (Box 48, Folder 896)
    - Lang, Cosmo Gordon, 1915-1942 (Box 48, Folder 897)
    - Lang, J. Henry, 1943-1947 (Box 48, Folder 898)
    - Lansdale, Herbert P., 1915-1955 (Box 48, Folder 899)
    - Lansing, Robert, 1916-1919 (Box 48, Folder 900)
    - Larsen, L.P., 1909 (Box 48, Folder 901)
    - Latourette, Kenneth Scott, 1932-1953 (Box 48, Folder 902)
    - Laubach, Frank C., 1938-1946 (Box 48, Folder 903)
    - Lawrence, William Laymen's Missionary Movement (see: F.J. Michel), 1908,1917 (Box 48, Folder 904)
    - League of Nations Association, 1940-1942 (Box 48, Folder 905)
    - Leaycraft, Edgar C. (see also: James Stokes Society), 1917-1950 (Box 48, Folder 906)
    - Leaycraft, Edgar C., 1951-1954 (Box 48, Folder 907)
    - Leber, Charles T., 1940-1947 (Box 48, Folder 908)
    - Lee, Edwin F., 1940-1946 (Box 48, Folder 909)
    - Lee, Elizabeth M., 1940-1952 (Box 48, Folder 910)
    - Leete, Frederick D., 1944-1953 (Box 48, Folder 911)
    - Lehtonen, Aleksi, 1946,,1947 (Box 48, Folder 912)
    - Leibert, Edwin R., 1940-1944 (Box 48, Folder 913)
    - Leiper, Henry Smith, 1940-1941 (Box 49, Folder 914)
    - Leiper, Henry Smith, 1942-1943 (Box 49, Folder 915)
    - Leiper, Henry Smith, 1944-1945 (Box 49, Folder 916)
    - Leiper, Henry Smith, 1946-1948 (Box 49, Folder 917)
    - Leiper, Henry Smith, 1949-1954 (Box 49, Folder 918)
    - Leland, Thad E., 1941-1942, nd. (Box 49, Folder 919)
    - Lenwood, Frank, 1918-1921 (Box 49, Folder 920)
    - Lenz, Frank B., 1940-1943 (Box 49, Folder 921)
    - Lenz, Frank B., 1944-1954 (Box 49, Folder 922)
    - Lerrigo, P.H.J., 1933-1945 (Box 49, Folder 923)
    - Leung, S.C., 1936-1954 (Box 49, Folder 924)
    - Lewis, Edwin N., 1940-1944 (Box 49, Folder 925)
    - Liberty Mutual Insurance Company, 1940-1953 (Box 49, Folder 926)
    - Lichtwardt, H.H., 1934-1946 (Box 50, Folder 927)
    - Lie, Trygve, 1946-1947 (Box 50, Folder 928)
    - Liebenberg, F.J., 1940-1948 (Box 50, Folder 929)
    - Lightbody, H.C., 1925-1940 (Box 50, Folder 930)
    - Lilje, Banns, 1927-1950 (Box 50, Folder 931)
    - Limbert, Paul M., 1945-1954 (Box 50, Folder 932)
    - Lind, Willy, 1945-1947 (Box 50, Folder 933)
    - Lindley, Alva E., 1941-1947 (Box 50, Folder 934)
    - Little, Grover J., 1935-1945 (Box 50, Folder 935)
    - Lockhart, James H., 1925-1937 (Box 50, Folder 936)
    - Long, Ralph H., 1942-1948 (Box 50, Folder 937)
    - Longfellow, Juha (Mrs. Frederick W.), 1940-1952 (Box 50, Folder 938)
    - Lothian, The Marquis of, 1936-1940 (Box 50, Folder 939)
    - Lotspeich, Edgar S., 1940-1944 (Box 50, Folder 940)
    - Lovett, A. Sidney, 1941-1944 (Box 50, Folder 941)
    - Low, Seth, 1901 (Box 50, Folder 942)
    - Lowrie, Donald A., 1930-1941 (Box 50, Folder 945)
    - Lowrie, Donald A., 1942-1948 (Box 50, Folder 944)
    - Lowrie, Donald A., 1949-1954 (Box 50, Folder 945)
    - Lowrie, Walter, 1920-1946 (Box 50, Folder 946)
    - Luce, Harry,Luce, 1940-1941 (Box 51, Folder 947)
    - Ludwig, Frederick R., 1940-1953 (Box 51, Folder 948)
    - Lundahl, Jakob E., 1925-1948 (Box 51, Folder 949)
    - Lvoff, Vladimir, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 950)
    - Lyon, Adrian, 1931 (Box 51, Folder 951)
    - Lyon, D. Willard, 1900-1949 (Box 51, Folder 952)
    - Lyon, Grace M., 1950-1952 (Box 51, Folder 953)
    - Mea - McC (Box 52, Folder 954)
    - MacD - McG (Box 52, Folder 955)
    - Macho- McK (Box 52, Folder 956)
    - scab -Stacy (Box 52, Folder 957)
    - Mad - Man (Box 52, Folder 958)
    - Mar (Box 52, Folder 959)
    - Mas - Mat (Box 52, Folder 960)
    - Mea - Merl (Box 52, Folder 961)
    - Mern - Mey (Box 52, Folder 962)
    - Mic - Millar (Box 52, Folder 963)
    - Miller (Box 52, Folder 964)
    - Milli - Mit (Box 52, Folder 965)
    - Mob - Mon (Box 52, Folder 966)
    - Moo - Mord (Box 52, Folder 967)
    - More - Moru (Box 52, Folder 968)
    - Mos - Mew (Box 52, Folder 969)
    - Mu - My (Box 52, Folder 970)
    - McBee, Silas, 1907-1922 (Box 53, Folder 971)
    - McBrier, Edwin, 1933-1948 (Box 53, Folder 972)
    - McBrier, Edwin, 1949-1955 (Box 53, Folder 973)
    - McClelland, Dalton F., 1939-1945 (Box 53, Folder 974)
    - McClelland, Dalton F., 1946- 1948 (Box 53, Folder 975)
    - McClelland, Dalton F., 1949-1954 (Box 53, Folder 976)
    - McConaughy, David, 1940-1946 (Box 53, Folder 977)
    - McConaughy, James M., 1903, 1910 (Box 53, Folder 978)
    - McConnell, Francis J., 1909-1948 (Box 53, Folder 979)
    - McConnell, J.J., 1941-1951 (Box 53, Folder 980)
    - McConnell, J.W., 1944-1954 (Box 53, Folder 981)
    - McCorkel, Roy, 1940-1946 (Box 53, Folder 982)
    - McCormick, Cyrus H. Jr., 1893-1935 (Box 53, Folder 983)
    - McCormick, Fowler, 1942 (Box 53, Folder 984)
    - McCormick, Gordon, 1942-1943 (Box 53, Folder 985)
    - McCormick, Nettie F., 1898 (Box 53, Folder 986)
    - McCormick, Nettie F., 1899 (Box 53, Folder 987)
    - McCormick, Nettie F., 1900-1901 (Box 53, Folder 988)
    - McCormick, Nettie F., 1902-1904 (Box 53, Folder 989)
    - McCormick, Nettie F., 1905-1906 (Box 54, Folder 990)
    - McCormick, Nettie F., 1907-1912 (Box 54, Folder 991)
    - McCormick, Nettie F., 1913-1915 (Box 54, Folder 992)
    - McCormick, Nettie F., 1916-1918 (Box 54, Folder 993)
    - McCormick, Nettie F., 1919-1921 (Box 54, Folder 994)
    - McCormick, Nettie F., 1922 (Box 54, Folder 995)
    - Nettie Fowler McCormick Biographical Assn., 1934-1954 (Box 54, Folder 996)
    - McCormick-Goodhart, L., 1944-1945 (Box 54, Folder 997)
    - McCowen, Oliver and Elizabeth, 1922-1954 (Box 54, Folder 998)
    - McDonald, J.W., 1942 (Box 54, Folder 999)
    - McDowell, William F., 1912-1933 (Box 54, Folder 1000)
    - Macfarland, Henry B., 1912-1921 (Box 54, Folder 1001)
    - McGavran, Donald, 1936-1940 (Box 54, Folder 1002)
    - MacGregor, James R., 1942-1954 (Box 54, Folder 1003)
    - MacInnes, Rennie, 1923,1928 (Box 54, Folder 1004)
    - McIntire, Charles C., 1940-1950 (Box 54, Folder 1005)
    - MacKay, John A., 1928-1954 (Box 54, Folder 1006)
    - McKee, Dean G., 1946-1954 (Box 54, Folder 1007)
    - McKenzie, John, 1915-1947 (Box 54, Folder 1008)
    - MacKenzie, W. Douglas, 1915-1935 (Box 54, Folder 1009)
    - Mackie, Robert C., 1932-1942 (Box 55, Folder 1010)
    - Mackie, Robert C., 1943-1945 (Box 55, Folder 1011)
    - Mackie, Robert C., 1946-1952, nd. (Box 55, Folder 1012)
    - McKim, Judson J., 1928-1948 (Box 55, Folder 1013)
    - MacKinnon, Sallie Lou, 1939-1943 (Box 55, Folder 1014)
    - MoLachlin, Louis E., 1940-1942 (Box 55, Folder 1015)
    - Maclay, Lord, 1925-1949 (Box 55, Folder 1016)
    - Maclean, J.H., 1895-1944 (Box 55, Folder 1017)
    - McLeish, Alexander, 1940-1946 (Box 55, Folder 1018)
    - Maclennan, Kenneth, 1909-1918 (Box 55, Folder 1019)
    - Maclennan, Kenneth, 1925-1952 (Box 55, Folder 1020)
    - Macleod, George F., 1941-1947 (Box 55, Folder 1021)
    - McMains, Harrison, 1944-1952 (Box 56, Folder 1022)
    - Macmillan Company, 1940-1944 (Box 56, Folder 1023)
    - MacMillan, Hugh, 1941-1947 (Box 56, Folder 1024)
    - Macnair, James I., 1940-1954 (Box 56, Folder 1025)
    - Macnicoll, N., 1933-1947 (Box 56, Folder 1026)
    - McTyier, J. Floyd, 1928-1954 (Box 56, Folder 1027)
    - McWilliams, D.W., 1908-1915 (Box 56, Folder 1028)
    - McWilliams, R.F., 1922-1954 (Box 56, Folder 1029)
    - Maddry, Charles E., 1940-1943 (Box 56, Folder 1030)
    - Madison, Ward, 1947-1954 (Box 56, Folder 1031)
    - Magee, J. Ralph, 1940-1948 (Box 56, Folder 1032)
    - Manikam, Rajah, 1940-1948 (Box 56, Folder 1033)
    - Manley, John E., 1912-1959 (Box 56, Folder 1034)
    - Manley, John E., 1940 (Box 56, Folder 1035)
    - Manley, John E., 1941 (Box 56, Folder 1036)
    - Manley, John E., 1942 (Box 56, Folder 1037)
    - Manley, John E., 1943 (Box 56, Folder 1038)
    - Manley, John E., 1944-1945 (Box 56, Folder 1039)
    - Manley, John E., 1946-1954 (Box 56, Folder 1040)
    - Manning, William T., 1923-1948 (Box 57, Folder 1041)
    - Mar, C.J., 1940-1949 (Box 57, Folder 1042)
    - Mar Kurilow, Metropolitan of Malabar, 1913 (Box 57, Folder 1043)
    - Mar Thoma, Abraham, Suffragan Metropolitan -- Mar Thoma Syrian Church of Malabar, 1937 (Box 57, Folder 1044)
    - Mar Thoma, Titus, Syrian Metropolitan, 1936-1937 (Box 57, Folder 1045)
    - Margaret, Crown Princess of Sweden, 1916-1917 (Box 57, Folder 1046)
    - Marie, (Queen of Rumania?), 1913 (Box 57, Folder 1047)
    - Marling, Alfred E., 1899-1934 (Box 57, Folder 1048)
    - Marquis, Sarah, 1939-1946 (Box 57, Folder 1049)
    - Marshall, Katherine, 1915-1950, nd (Box 57, Folder 1050)
    - Marston, George W., 1921-1946 (Box 57, Folder 1051)
    - Martin, Anna P., 1941-1942 (Box 57, Folder 1052)
    - Martin, G. Harold, 1948-1949 (Box 57, Folder 1053)
    - Martin, Horace Ford, 1940-1942 (Box 57, Folder 1054)
    - Martin, Horace Ford, 1943-1945 (Box 57, Folder 1055)
    - Martin, Horace Ford, 1946-1949, nd (Box 57, Folder 1056)
    - Martin, Hugh, 1942-1950 (Box 57, Folder 1057)
    - Martin, W.N., 1948-1952, nd (Box 57, Folder 1058)
    - Masaryck, Tomas G. and Olga G., 1920-1925 (Box 57, Folder 1059)
    - Massey, C.D., 1902-1912 (Box 57, Folder 1060)
    - Massey, Vincent, 1920-1928 (Box 57, Folder 1061)
    - Massey, Vincent, 1929-1930 (Box 57, Folder 1062)
    - Massey, Vincent, 1931-1948 (Box 57, Folder 1063)
    - Mateer, Calvin and Julia, 1896-1898 (Box 58, Folder 1064)
    - Mather, Samuel and Flora, 1905-1917 (Box 58, Folder 1065)
    - Mathews, Basil, 1924-1941 (Box 58, Folder 1066)
    - Mathews, Basil, 1942-1945 (Box 58, Folder 1067)
    - Mathews, Basil, 1946-1951 (Box 58, Folder 1068)
    - Mathews, Shailer, 1909,1940 (Box 58, Folder 1069)
    - Matsumoto, Toru, 1940-1942 (Box 58, Folder 1070)
    - Maury, Pierre, 1933-1953 (Box 58, Folder 1071)
    - Mays, Benjamin E., 1939-1940 (Box 58, Folder 1072)
    - Mays, Benjamin E., 1942-1949 (Box 58, Folder 1073)
    - Meeker, Arthur Y., 1942-1944 (Box 58, Folder 1074)
    - Meigs, John, 1907-1909 (Box 58, Folder 1075)
    - Meletios, Patriarch of Alexandria, 1926,1930 (Box 58, Folder 1076)
    - Meletius, Metropolitan of Athens, 1920 (Box 58, Folder 1080)
    - Mendenhall, W.W., 1940-1948 (Box 58, Folder 1077)
    - Mendenhall, W.W., 1949-1952 (Box 58, Folder 1078)
    - Messer, L. Wilbur Episcopal Church Brd of Mssn. (see: J.F. Goucher 1908), 1916,1918 (Box 58, Folder 1079)
    - Meyer, Eugene, 1940-1944 (Box 58, Folder 1081)
    - Michaelis, Georg, 1922-1927 (Box 58, Folder 1082)
    - Michalson, Gordon E., 1947-1948 (Box 58, Folder 1083)
    - Michel, Frederick J., 1940-1942 (Box 58, Folder 1084)
    - Michel, Frederick J., 1943-1945 (Box 58, Folder 1085)
    - Michel, Frederick J., 1946-1952 (Box 58, Folder 1086)
    - Miller, Alvah L., 1940-1947 (Box 59, Folder 1087)
    - Miller, Francis P., 1915- 1927 May (Box 59, Folder 1088)
    - Miller, Francis P., 1927 Jun-Dec (Box 59, Folder 1089)
    - Miller, Francis P., 1928- Feb-Jun (Box 59, Folder 1090)
    - Miller, Francis P., 1928 Jul-Dec (Box 59, Folder 1091)
    - Miller, Francis P., 1929 (Box 59, Folder 1092)
    - Miller, Francis P., 1930-1947 (Box 59, Folder 1093)
    - Miller, J. Quinter, 1942-1944 (Box 59, Folder 1094)
    - Mills, David B., 1917-1940 (Box 59, Folder 1095)
    - Mills, David B., 1945-1947 (Box 59, Folder 1096)
    - Mills, Samuel J., 1941-1943 (Box 59, Folder 1097)
    - Mills, Victor G., 1933- 1948 (Box 59, Folder 1098)
    - Research Library (see: C. Fahs, R.P. Beaver)
    - Moltke, Joachim, 1898-1940, nd (Box 59, Folder 1099)
    - Montclair Trust Company, 1940-1944 (Box 59, Folder 1100)
    - Moomaw, Ira W., 1946-1951 (Box 59, Folder 1101)
    - Moore, Arthur J., 1942-1948 (Box 59, Folder 1102)
    - Moore, Emma C., 1935-1940 (Box 59, Folder 1103)
    - Moore, Fred Atkins, 1940-1945 (Box 59, Folder 1104)
    - Moore, John F., 1940-1948 (Box 59, Folder 1105)
    - Moran, Hugh, 1915-1952 (Box 60, Folder 1106)
    - Morehouse, Clifford P., 1940-1948 (Box 60, Folder 1107)
    - Morgan, Anne, 1917 (Box 60, Folder 1108)
    - Morris, Dave Hennen, 1940-1942 (Box 60, Folder 1109)
    - Morrison, Sara E., 1940-1945 (Box 60, Folder 1110)
    - Morse, Richard C., 1889-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1111)
    - Morse, Richard C., 1913-1925 (Box 60, Folder 1112)
    - Morton, Helen, 1940-1945 (Box 60, Folder 1113)
    - Morton, Fanny, Janie and Mary, 1941-1952 (Box 60, Folder 1114)
    - Moss, Leslie B., 1933-1946 (Box 60, Folder 1115)
    - Moton, Robert R., 1922-1935 (Box 60, Folder 1116)
    - Moule, Handley C.G., 1901-1910 (Box 60, Folder 1117)
    - Mudge, Lewis S., 1940-1945 (Box 60, Folder 1118)
    - Mudge, William L., 1941-1942 (Box 60, Folder 1119)
    - MUller, Joachim, 1928-1947 (Box 60, Folder 1120)
    - Murphy, Starr, 1910 (Box 60, Folder 1121)
    - Murray, Andrew, 1916 (Box 60, Folder 1122)
    - Murray, J. Lovell, 1933-1952 (Box 60, Folder 1123)
    - R.F. Murray and Bro., Inc., 1933-1942 (Box 60, Folder 1124)
    - Murray, William D., 1901-1936 (Box 60, Folder 1125)
    - Myers, Harry S., 1940-1949 (Box 60, Folder 1126)
    - Na (Box 61, Folder 1127)
    - Ne (Box 61, Folder 1128)
    - Ni - No (Box 61, Folder 1129)
    - Ny (Box 61, Folder 1130)
    - National City Bank of New York, 1942-1954 (Box 61, Folder 1131)
    - National City Bank of New York, 1942-1954 (Box 61, Folder 1132)
    - National War Fund, Inc., 1943-1947 (Box 61, Folder 1133)
    - Nausen, F., 1921 (Box 61, Folder 1134)
    - Neblett, S.A., 1939-1945 (Box 61, Folder 1135)
    - Neely, Thomas B., 1905 (Box 61, Folder 1136)
    - Nehru, Jawaharlal, 1936 (Box 61, Folder 1137)
    - Neill, Stephen C., 1939, 1947 (Box 61, Folder 1138)
    - Nelson, Claud D., 1924-1944 (Box 61, Folder 1139)
    - Nelson, Claud D., 1945-1953 (Box 61, Folder 1140)
    - Neuendorffer, Esther, 1952-1953, nd (Box 62, Folder 1141)
    - New York Herald Tribune, 1940-1949 (Box 62, Folder 1142)
    - New York Telephone Company, 1939-1942 (Box 62, Folder 1143)
    - New York Times, 1940-1953 (Box 62, Folder 1144)
    - Newton, Louie D., 1946-1948 (Box 62, Folder 1145)
    - Nicholson, Thomas and Evelyn, 1916-1947, nd (Box 62, Folder 1146)
    - Nicholai, Bishop of Serbia, 1941-1948 (Box 62, Folder 1147)
    - Nicolai, Archbishop, 1904,1909 (Box 62, Folder 1148)
    - Niebuhr, Reinhold, 1931-1953 (Box 62, Folder 1149)
    - Niles, D.T., 1940-1947 (Box 62, Folder 1150)
    - Niwa, S., 1930-1949 (Box 62, Folder 1151)
    - Nobel, Emanuel, 1917 (Box 62, Folder 1152)
    - Noble, Walter J., 1934-1948 (Box 62, Folder 1153)
    - North, Eric M., 1940- 1947 (Box 62, Folder 1154)
    - North, Frank Mason, 1905-1934 (Box 62, Folder 1155)
    - Nystrom, Joel E., 1943-1952 (Box 62, Folder 1156)
    - Ob - Oh (Box 62, Folder 1157)
    - Ol- Ox (Box 62, Folder 1158)
    - Ober, Charles K., 1886-1889 (Box 62, Folder 1159)
    - Ober, Charles K., 1890-1901 (Box 62, Folder 1160)
    - Ober, Charles K., 1915-1948, nd (Box 62, Folder 1161)
    - Oberlin Colloge re: Presidency (see: Mills, Charles S. Wheeler, Benjamin), 1895 Mar 1898 Mar
    - O'Brien, R.D., 1942-1945 (Box 63, Folder 1162)
    - Odell, E A. Ohio Wesieyan University (See:Bashford, J.W.), 1939-1940 (Box 63, Folder 1163)
    - Olcott, Mason, 1940-1948 (Box 63, Folder 1164)
    - Oldham, G.Ashton, 1940-1948 (Box 63, Folder 1165)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1904, 1908 (Box 63, Folder 1166)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1909 Jan-Jun (Box 63, Folder 1167)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1909 Jul-Dec (Box 63, Folder 1168)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1910 Jan-Apr (Box 63, Folder 1169)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1910 Oct-Dec (Box 63, Folder 1170)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1911 Jan-Apr (Box 63, Folder 1171)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1911 May-Dec (Box 63, Folder 1172)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1912 Jan-Jun (Box 63, Folder 1173)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1912 Jul-Dec (Box 63, Folder 1174)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1913 Jan-Aug (Box 64, Folder 1175)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1913 Sep-Dec (Box 64, Folder 1176)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1914 Jan-May (Box 64, Folder 1177)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1914 Jun-Aug (Box 64, Folder 1178)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1914 Sep-Dec (Box 64, Folder 1179)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1915 Jan-Mar (Box 64, Folder 1180)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1915 Apr-Aug (Box 64, Folder 1181)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1915 Sep-Dec (Box 64, Folder 1182)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1916 (Box 64, Folder 1183)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1917 (Box 64, Folder 1184)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1918 (Box 65, Folder 1185)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1919 (Box 65, Folder 1186)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1920 (Box 65, Folder 1187)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1921 Feb-Apr (Box 65, Folder 1188)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1921 May-Dec (Box 65, Folder 1189)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1922 (Box 65, Folder 1190)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1923-1924 (Box 65, Folder 1191)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1925 (Box 65, Folder 1192)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1926 (Box 65, Folder 1193)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1927 (Box 65, Folder 1194)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1928 (Box 66, Folder 1195)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1929 (Box 66, Folder 1196)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1930 (Box 66, Folder 1197)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1931 (Box 66, Folder 1198)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1932 (Box 66, Folder 1199)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1933 (Box 66, Folder 1200)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1934 (Box 66, Folder 1201)
    - Oldham, Joseph H. - correspondence re: Nobel Peace Prize for JRM, 1932-1934 (Box 66, Folder 1202)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1935 (Box 66, Folder 1203)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1936 (Box 66, Folder 1204)
    - Oldham, Joseph B., 1937 (Box 66, Folder 1205)
    - Oldham, Joseph H., 1938-1952 (Box 66, Folder 1206)
    - Olds, Ransom E., 1940-1949 (Box 66, Folder 1207)
    - Oliver, B. Chone, 1938-1943 (Box 66, Folder 1208)
    - Olson, Inez L., 1943-1952, nd (Box 66, Folder 1209)
    - Olson, Oscar T., 1947-1951 (Box 66, Folder 1210)
    - Oxnam, G. Bromley, 1939-1954 (Box 66, Folder 1211)
    - Paa - Pai (Box 67, Folder 1212)
    - Pal - Pas (Box 67, Folder 1213)
    - Pat - Pc (Box 67, Folder 1214)
    - Pea - Pep (Box 67, Folder 1215)
    - Per - Pey (Box 67, Folder 1216)
    - Ph (Box 67, Folder 1217)
    - Pi (Box 67, Folder 1218)
    - PI - Pol. (Box 67, Folder 1219)
    - Pon - Pou (Box 67, Folder 1220)
    - Pr (Box 67, Folder 1221)
    - Pu - Py (Box 67, Folder 1222)
    - Packard, Arthur W., 1930-1938 (Box 67, Folder 1223)
    - Packard, Arthur W., 1940-1942 (Box 67, Folder 1224)
    - Packard, Arthur W., 1943-1948 (Box 67, Folder 1225)
    - Paddock, Robert, 1927-1929 (Box 67, Folder 1226)
    - Paddock, Robert, 1930-1937 (Box 67, Folder 1227)
    - Paddock, Robert, 1938-1940 (Box 67, Folder 1228)
    - Pain, E. Maynard, 1896, 1913 (Box 67, Folder 1229)
    - Pangborn, Cyrus R., 1942-1944 (Box 67, Folder 1230)
    - Panaretoff, S., 1912-1917 (Box 67, Folder 1231)
    - Parker, Joseph I., 1940-1947 (Box 67, Folder 1232)
    - Pascoe, Juan N., 1943-1954 (Box 68, Folder 1233)
    - Paterson, Arthur L., 1914-1952 (Box 68, Folder 1234)
    - Paterson, Charles S., 1897,1940-1946,nd (Box 68, Folder 1235)
    - Paton, David (Box 68, Folder 1236)
    - Paton, Frank H. L., 1913, 1926 (Box 68, Folder 1237)
    - Paton, William, 1913-1927 Jul (Box 68, Folder 1238)
    - Paton, William, 1927 Sep-Dec (Box 68, Folder 1239)
    - Paton, William, 1928 Jan-May (Box 68, Folder 1240)
    - Paton, William, 1928 Jun-Dec (Box 68, Folder 1241)
    - Paton, William, 1929 (Box 68, Folder 1242)
    - Paton, William, 1930 Feb-Aug (Box 68, Folder 1243)
    - Paton, William, 1930 Sep-Dec (Box 68, Folder 1244)
    - Paton, William, 1931 Feb-Jul (Box 68, Folder 1245)
    - Paton, William, 1931 Sep-Dec (Box 68, Folder 1246)
    - Paton, William, 1932 (Box 68, Folder 1247)
    - Paton, William, 1933-1934 (Box 68, Folder 1248)
    - Paton, William, 1935 (Box 68, Folder 1249)
    - Paton, William, 1936-1938 (Box 69, Folder 1250)
    - Paton, William, 1939 (Box 69, Folder 1251)
    - Paton, William, 1940 (Box 69, Folder 1252)
    - Paton, William, 1941 (Box 69, Folder 1253)
    - Paton, William, 1942 (Box 69, Folder 1254)
    - Paton, William, 1943 (Box 69, Folder 1255)
    - Paton, William-notes and tributes, 1943, nd (Box 69, Folder 1256)
    - Paton, Mrs.William and children, 1940-1949 (Box 69, Folder 1257)
    - Patton, T.D., 1904-1941 (Box 69, Folder 1258)
    - Paul, C.S., 1948-1952 (Box 69, Folder 1259)
    - Paul, K.T., 1917-1930 (Box 69, Folder 1260)
    - Peabody, Francis G., 1901-1933 (Box 69, Folder 1261)
    - Peabody, Lucy, 1938-1949 (Box 69, Folder 1262)
    - Peabody, Malcolm E., 1946-1949 (Box 69, Folder 1263)
    - Pelham, William F., 1944-1945 (Box 70, Folder 1264)
    - Pence, Owen E., 1915-1950 (Box 70, Folder 1265)
    - Pendleton, Ellen F., 1924, 1930 (Box 70, Folder 1266)
    - Penfield, Thornton G., Jr., 1942-1947 (Box 70, Folder 1267)
    - Penn Mutual Life Insurance, 1932-1947 (Box 70, Folder 1268)
    - Pepper, George Wharton, 1914-1950 (Box 70, Folder 1269)
    - Perkins, George W., 1913-1945 (Box 70, Folder 1270)
    - Pershing, John J., 1918-1941 (Box 70, Folder 1271)
    - Peter, Agnes (see also Series II - Agnes Peter Mott), 1940-1950 (Box 70, Folder 1272)
    - Petitt, C.W., 1943-1949 (Box 70, Folder 1273)
    - Pettus, William B., 1910-1941 (Box 70, Folder 1274)
    - Pfeiffer, Mrs. Henry, 1936-1946 (Box 70, Folder 1275)
    - Pflager, Henry B., 1940-1942 (Box 70, Folder 1276)
    - Phelps, G. Sidney, 1913-1943 (Box 70, Folder 1277)
    - Phelps, G. Sidney, 1949-1951 (Box 70, Folder 1278)
    - Phildius, Christian, 1908-1936 (Box 70, Folder 1279)
    - Phildius, Eberhard, 1911-1946 (Box 70, Folder 1280)
    - Phildius, Eberhard, 1947-1948 (Box 70, Folder 1281)
    - Phildius, Eberhard, 1949-1952 (Box 70, Folder 1282)
    - Phillips, Ray E., 1940-1946 (Box 70, Folder 1283)
    - Phillips, William, 1938, nd (Box 70, Folder 1284)
    - Pianoff, Th., 1945-1949 (Box 70, Folder 1285)
    - Pidgeon, George C., 1941-1946 (Box 70, Folder 1286)
    - Pierrel, Gren 0., 1940-1945 (Box 70, Folder 1287)
    - Pierson, Delavan, 1933-1950 (Box 70, Folder 1288)
    - Pinchot, Gifford, 1908-1931 (Box 71, Folder 1289)
    - Platon, Metropolitan of Russian Orthodox Church, 1919-1924 (Box 71, Folder 1290)
    - Poling, Daniel, 1936-1949 (Box 71, Folder 1291)
    - Ponsford, T.R., 1940-1945 (Box 71, Folder 1292)
    - Pontius, John H., 1915-1949 (Box 71, Folder 1293)
    - Pope, Liston, 1950 (Box 71, Folder 1294)
    - Porter, David R., 1925-1944 (Box 71, Folder 1295)
    - Porter, David R., 1945-1946 (Box 71, Folder 1296)
    - Porter, David R., 1947-1955 nd (Box 71, Folder 1297)
    - Porter, Mary A., 1945-1946 (Box 71, Folder 1298)
    - Post, James H., 1927 (Box 71, Folder 1299)
    - Potter, F.M., 1940-1949 (Box 71, Folder 1300)
    - Potts, J. Manning, 1940-1950 (Box 71, Folder 1301)
    - Powell, Noble C., 1940-1941 (Box 71, Folder 1302)
    - Price, Frank W., 1940-1948 (Box 71, Folder 1303)
    - Price, P. Frank, 1941-1948 (Box 71, Folder 1304)